Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Park, 166661
  - Subseries H: General Views, 166662
    - General Views - People (3 of 3), circa 1980-1989; 166678 (Box 216, Folder 3)
      - Jogger in Jog-a-thon, 1980; wsp_gv_9_3_43; 166692; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 43)
      - Jogger during Jog-a-thon, 1980; wsp_gv_9_3_44; 166691; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 44)
      - People Juggling, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_45; 166690; Rodriguez, Robert F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 45)
      - People in Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_46; 166689; Rodriguez, Robert F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 46)
      - Garibaldi Statue, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_47; 166688; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 47)
      - Fountain, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_48; 166687; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 48)
      - People Walking in a Row, 1973; wsp_gv_9_3_49; 166686; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 49)
      - Reconstruction of Washington Square Park Sign, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_50; 166685; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 50)
      - Poles on Perimeter of Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_51; 166684; black-and-white print (photograph), 7 x 9 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 51)
      - Poles on Perimeter of Park, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_52; 166683; black-and-white print (photograph), 7 x 9 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 52)
      - Performer and Camera Crew, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_53; 166682; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 53)
      - Man Sleeping, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_54; 166681; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 54)
      - Musician, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_55; 166680; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 55)
      - Street Vendor, undated; wsp_gv_9_3_56; 166679; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 216, Folder 3, Item 56)
    - Restoration Plan, 1964; 166675 (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - Plan: Washington Square Park, Aerial View, 1964; wsp_rp_10_1_01; 166677; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Aerial Plan of Washington Square Park, undated; wsp_rp_10_1_02; 166676; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Statues, 1890-1960; 166665 (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - Soldiers Marching Near Garibaldi Statue, 1944; wsp_st_10_2_01; 166674; Sozio, A.F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Garibaldi Statue, undated; wsp_st_10_2_02; 166673; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Man Sitting at Base of Garibaldi Statue, 1991; wsp_st_10_2_03; 166672; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Snow Sculpture, undated; wsp_st_10_2_04; 166671; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 4)
      - Statue of Alexander Lyman Holley, 1905; wsp_st_10_2_05; 166670; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 5)
      - Italian Centenary Celebrants at Garibaldi Statue, circa 1956 - 1960; wsp_st_10_2_06; 166669; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 6)
      - Crowd Around Garibaldi Statue, 1955; wsp_st_10_2_07; 166668; Gooen, Irwin; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 7)
      - Garibaldi Statue, undated; wsp_st_10_2_08; 166667; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 217, Folder 2, Item 8)
      - Postcard of Park and Garibaldi Statue, undated; wsp_st_10_2_09; 166666; color print (postcard), 4 x 6inches (Box 217, Folder 3, Item 9)
    - Winter Scenes, undated; 166664 (Box 217, Folder 3)
      contact sheets
    - Exhibit Photos, 1889-1990; 166663 (Box 217, Folder 4)
      (8 photos mounted on foam core)
    - Company F - 3202 SCSU ASTU NYU, 1944-03-04 (Flat-file-folder 7 Tray 1)
- Washington Square Area, 166005
  This series contains photographs and prints of the Washington Square vicinity.
  - Astor Place Subway, circa 1975-1985; 166647 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Eighth Street Subway Station, undated; wsa_aps_1_1_01; 166660; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Astor Subway Station, circa 1975 - 1985; wsa_aps_1_1_02; 166659; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Subway Car Interior, circa 1975 - 1985; wsa_aps_1_1_03; 166658; Rhyins, Will; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Astor Place Subway Station, circa 1980 - 1989; wsa_aps_1_1_04; 166657; Rhyins, Will; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Astor Place Subway Station, 1980; wsa_aps_1_1_05; 166656; Friedman, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Astor Place Subway Station, 1980; wsa_aps_1_1_06; 166655; Friedman, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Astor Place Subway Station, circa 1975 - 1985; wsa_aps_1_1_07; 166654; Rhyins, Will; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Astor Place Subway Station, circa 1975 - 1985; wsa_aps_1_1_08; 166653; Rhyins, Will; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Astor Place Subway Station, circa 1975 - 1985; wsa_aps_1_1_09; 166652; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Astor Place Subway Station, circa 1975 - 1985; wsa_aps_1_1_10; 166651; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Eighth Street Subway Station, 1970; wsa_aps_1_1_11; 166650; Moore, Peter; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Eighth Street Subway Station, 1970; wsa_aps_1_1_12; 166649; Moore, Peter; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Eighth Street Subway Station, 1970; wsa_aps_1_1_13; 166648; Moore, Peter; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 1, Item 13)
  - 693 Broadway, circa 1965 - 1975; 166638 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - 693 Broadway, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_1_2_01; 166646; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - 693 Broadway, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_1_2_02; 166645; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - 693 Broadway (Detail), circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_1_2_03; 166644; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - 693 Broadway, wsa_1_2_04; 166643; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - Coffee Shop, 693 Broadway, wsa_1_2_05; 166642; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - 693 Broadway, wsa_1_2_06; 166641; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - 693 Broadway, wsa_1_2_07; 166640; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - 693 Broadway (Detail), wsa_1_2_08; 166639; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 2, Item 8)
  - Basketball Court - West 4th Street, 1981; 166632 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Basketball Game, undated; wsa_1_3_01; 166637; DuBois, Gaston; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Basketball Game, 1981; wsa_1_3_02; 166636; Pena, John; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Basketball Game, 1981; wsa_1_3_03; 166635; Pena, John; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Basketball Game, 1981; wsa_1_3_04; 166634; Pena, John; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Basketball Game, 1981; wsa_1_3_05; 166633; Pena, John; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Bleecker Street, 1955-1983; 166602 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Bleecker Street Cinema, Bleecker Between West Broadway and Thompson, wsa_1_4_01; 166631; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Greenwich Hotel, Bleecker Looking West Toward Sullivan, undated; wsa_1_4_02; 166630; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Yipster Front, 1981; wsa_1_4_03; 166629; Slavkovsky, R.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Bleecker Street Between MacDougal and Sullivan, undated; wsa_1_4_04; 166628; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Bleecker Street Cinema Marquee, undated; wsa_1_4_05; 166627; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - Bleecker Street Between West Broadway and Thompson, undated; wsa_1_4_06; 166626; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Building, East End of Bleecker Street, undated; wsa_1_4_07; 166625; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 7)
    - Bleecker Street Between MacDougal and Sullivan, undated; wsa_1_4_08; 166624; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 8)
    - Bleecker Street at Sullivan Street, undated; wsa_1_4_09; 166623; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - Bleecker Street at Thompson Street, undated; wsa_1_4_10; 166622; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - Phone Booths, Bleecker Street, 1983; wsa_1_4_11; 166621; Chait, Marc W.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 11)
    - Saint Barnabas House, 1983; wsa_1_4_12; 166620; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 12)
    - Corner of Bleecker and Mulberry Streets, 1983; wsa_1_4_13; 166619; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 13)
    - Bleecker Bob's Records, 1983; wsa_1_4_14; 166618; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 14)
    - Cafe Rafio, undated; wsa_1_4_15; 166617; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 15)
    - Bleecker Street Between Thompson and West Broadway, undated; wsa_1_4_16; 166616; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 16)
    - 175 Bleecker Street, undated; wsa_1_4_17; 166615; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 17)
    - Men on Bleecker Street, Looking East Toward Thompson, undated; wsa_1_4_18; 166614; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 18)
    - Ganga's Used Clothing Store, Undated; wsa_1_4_19; 166613; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 19)
    - Folk City, undated; wsa_1_4_20; 166612; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 20)
    - Deli-Box Restaurant, Bleecker Street, undated; wsa_1_4_21; 166611; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 21)
    - Bleecker Street Between Greene and Mercer, 1955; wsa_1_4_22; 166610; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 22)
    - Looking North Up Thompson Street, undated; wsa_1_4_23; 166609; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 23)
    - Bleecker and Sullivan Streets, undated; wsa_1_4_24; 166608; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 24)
    - New York Switchboard Peoples Information Center, undated; wsa_1_4_25; 166607; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 25)
    - New York Switchboard Peoples Information Center, undated; wsa_1_4_26; 166606; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 26)
    - New York Switchboard Peoples Information Center, undated; wsa_1_4_27; 166605; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 27)
    - Ambulance, Mercer and Bleecker Streets, undated; wsa_1_4_28; 166604; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 28)
    - Saint Baranabas House, Interior, 1983; wsa_1_4_29; 166603; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 4, Item 29)
  - Broadway, circa 1964-1990; 166585 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - 640 Broadway at West 4th Street, wsa_1_5_01; 166601; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - 640 Broadway at West 4th Street, undated; wsa_1_5_02; 166600; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Costume Shop Window, undated; wsa_1_5_03; 166599; Rodriguez, Robert F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Billy Idol Fans Waiting in Line for Tickets, circa 1980 - 1990; wsa_1_5_04; 166598; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Child with Pumpkin Toy, wsa_1_5_05; 166597; Rodriguez, Robert F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 5)
    - 707 Broadway, 1964; wsa_1_5_06; 166596; Luigi Pellettieri; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 6)
    - Crowd Outside of Tower Records, 1984; wsa_1_5_07; 166595; Chen, Andy; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 7)
    - Tower Records, 1983; wsa_1_5_08; 166594; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 8)
    - 657 Broadway, 1981; wsa_1_5_09; 166593; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 9)
    - 561 Broadway, 1979; wsa_1_5_10; 166592; Smith, Jeff; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 10)
    - 561 Broadway, 1979; wsa_1_5_11; 166591; Smith, Jeff; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 11)
    - Building with Scaffolding, undated; wsa_1_5_12; 166590; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 12)
    - Church, undated; wsa_1_5_13; 166589; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 13)
    - People Waiting in Line Outside of Tower Records, undated; wsa_1_5_14; 166588; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 14)
    - 561 Broadway, undated; wsa_1_5_15; 166587; Smith, Jeff; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 15)
    - People Waiting in Line Outside of Tower Records, undated; wsa_1_5_16; 166586; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 175, Folder 5, Item 16)
  - Church of the Strangers, Mercer Street, 166583 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Church of the Stranger, Mercer Street (engraving), wsa_1_6_01; 166584; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 175, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Clinton Court (drawing), 1854; 166581 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Clinton Court - Drawn Map of Area Between 6th Avenue, 8th Street, Waverly Place and MacDougal Street, 1854; wsa_1_7_01; 166582; Perris, William; Paper Reproduction of Drawn Map Taped onto 8 x 10 Paper (Box 175, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - General views -Contact Sheets, Miscellaneous, 166580 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    Contact sheets
  - Diners, Cafes, Restaurants (1 of 2), 166512 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - "Rocks in Your Head" Record Shop, 1981; wsa_2_1_01; 166579; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - "Rocks in Your Head" Record Shop, 1981; wsa_2_1_02; 166578; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - "Rocks in Your Head" Record Shop (interior), 1981; wsa_2_1_03; 166577; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Waitress, Cafe Rosa Diner, undated; wsa_2_1_04; 166576; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Tio Pepe Cafe (exterior), undated; wsa_2_1_05; 166575; black-and-white print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Cook, New Dehli Restaurant, 1983; wsa_2_1_06; 166574; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Arch Cafe, Washington Square South and Thompson Streets, 1905; wsa_2_1_07; 166573; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Cafe Figaro, undated; wsa_2_1_08; 166572; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Barista, undated; wsa_2_1_09; 166571; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Restaurant Interior, undated; wsa_2_1_10; 166570; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Cafe Borgia, undated; wsa_2_1_11; 166569; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Campus Coffee Shop, undated; wsa_2_1_12; 166568 (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Cafe, undated; wsa_2_1_13; 166567; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - Buffalo Roadhouse, 1975; wsa_2_1_14; 166566 (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Villa Marbona Italian Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_15; 166565; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 5 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 15)
    - Campus Coffee Shop and Environs, From Above, 1965; wsa_2_1_16; 166564; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Menu, The Captain's Table, undated; wsa_2_1_17; 166563 (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Cook in Cafeteria, undated; wsa_2_1_18; 166562; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 18)
    - Cook, Loeb Commons Cafeteria, 1980; wsa_2_1_19; 166561; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 19)
    - Cook, Cafeteria, undated; wsa_2_1_20; 166560; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 20)
    - Dirty Floor, Loeb Cafeteria, undated; wsa_2_1_21; 166559; Morris, R.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 21)
    - Trinity Place, undated; wsa_2_1_22; 166558; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 22)
    - Restaurant (interior), undated; wsa_2_1_23; 166557; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 23)
    - Pantry, Loeb Cafeteria, undated; wsa_2_1_24; 166556; Morris, R.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 24)
    - Store Interior, undated; wsa_2_1_25; 166555; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 25)
    - The Captain's Table, undated; wsa_2_1_26; 166554; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 6 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 26)
    - Produce Market, undated; wsa_2_1_27; 166553; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 27)
    - "The Loading Zone", 1981; wsa_2_1_28; 166552; Friedman, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 28)
    - Caffe Pane e Cioccolato, 1981; wsa_2_1_29; 166551; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 29)
    - Granados Cafe, undated; wsa_2_1_30; 166550; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 30)
    - Star of Siam Restaurant (interior), 1983; wsa_2_1_31; 166549; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 31)
    - Wok Restaurant, 1980; wsa_2_1_32; 166548; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 32)
    - Hopper's Restaurant and Market, 1976; wsa_2_1_33; 166547; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 33)
    - Star of Siam Restaurant (interior), 1983; wsa_2_1_34; 166546; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 34)
    - Rocks in Your Head Record Shop (interior), 1981; wsa_2_1_35; 166545; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 35)
    - Record, 1981; wsa_2_1_36; 166544; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 36)
    - The Cookery, undated; wsa_2_1_37; 166543; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 37)
    - Luncheonette, undated; wsa_2_1_38; 166542; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 38)
    - Espresso Machine, undated; wsa_2_1_39; 166541; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 39)
    - Man, undated; wsa_2_1_40; 166540; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 40)
    - Man, Rock and Roll Pizza, undated; wsa_2_1_41; 166539; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 41)
    - La Groceria Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_42; 166538; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 42)
    - La Groceria Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_43; 166537; Chin, Danny; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 43)
    - Lone Star Cafe, 13th Street and 5th Avenue, undated; wsa_2_1_44; 166536; Smith, Jeff; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 44)
    - Star of Siam Restaurant (interior), undated; wsa_2_1_45; 166535; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 45)
    - Star of Siam Restaurant (interior), 1983; wsa_2_1_46; 166534; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 46)
    - Steve's Ice Cream Shop, 1983; wsa_2_1_47; 166533; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 47)
    - Dual Pallete Restaurant (interior), undated; wsa_2_1_48; 166532; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 48)
    - Waitress, Cafe Rosa, undated; wsa_2_1_49; 166531; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 49)
    - Waiter, Dual Pallete Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_50; 166530; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 50)
    - The Pitaria, 1984; wsa_2_1_51; 166529; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 51)
    - Xenia II Greek Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_52; 166528; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 52)
    - Baked Goods at the Pitaria, 1984; wsa_2_1_53; 166527; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 53)
    - Quantum Leap Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_54; 166526; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 54)
    - Quantum Leap Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_55; 166525; Messer, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 55)
    - The Pitaria, 1984; wsa_2_1_56; 166524; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 56)
    - Tio Pepe Restaurant, undated; wsa_2_1_57; 166523; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 176, Folder 1, Item 57)